bloggingheads.tv 2019-06-21

# Bloggingheads.tv

This Privacy Policy governs the way we collect and use information from visitors to Bloggingheads.tv.

## Personal identification information

We do not collect personal information about visitors to our website unless you choose to provide that information to us via our contact form or email subscription (see below).

### Contact form

We provide a contact form on Bloggingheads.tv so that site visitors can communicate with us. Users of this optional service provide a name as well as an email address where they can receive a response when one is needed. We do not use this information for any purpose other than responding to inquiries and we do not share this information with third parties.

### Email subscriptions

We allow users to subscribe to our content through the email delivery features of Google’s FeedBurner application. Users of this optional service provide an email address where they want to receive Bloggingheads.tv subscription emails. We do not use these email addresses for any purpose other than Bloggingheads.tv email subscriptions and we do not share them with third parties.

### Disqus commenting system

We use the Disqus commenting system to collect and display comments about content on Bloggingheads.tv. Disqus is an independent web application with its own privacy policy. If you log in and comment through Disqus, your comments and information, including personal information such as your email address, are subject to the [privacy policy of Disqus](http://help.disqus.com/customer/portal/articles/466259-privacy-policy). We are not responsible for the privacy of information transmitted through the Disqus commenting system, even though it is accessed via our webpages.

We may occasionally look up an email address of a commenter via the administration panel available to us as Disqus moderators, in order to communicate privately with the commenter. We do not use these email addresses for any other purpose and we do not share them with outside parties.

### CafePress shop

We sell branded merchandise in our “shop” on the CafePress website. CafePress is an independent website with its own privacy policy. If you purchase merchandise on CafePress, your information, including personal information such as your email address, is subject to the [privacy policy of CafePress](http://www.cafepress.com/cp/info/help/index.aspx?page=privacy_policy.aspx). We are not responsible for the privacy of information transmitted on CafePress.

## Nonpersonal identification information

When you visit Bloggingheads.tv, we automatically gather and store some bits of nonpersonal information about your visit, so we can track the use of our website and make improvements. This information is stored and used in the aggregate only—no data is stored about your own individual visit that can be linked to you personally. The collected information includes:

  * the type of computer, operating system and browser used to access Bloggingheads.tv
  * the IP address from which you access Bloggingheads.tv
  * the internet address of the website from which you navigate to Bloggingheads.tv
  * the date and time you access Bloggingheads.tv
  * the pages, files, documents and links that you visit on Bloggingheads.tv

## Cookies

Cookies are bits of computer code stored on your own computer by a website that you visit. Cookies are often used to track a website’s usage patterns, traffic trends and user behavior. Many content adjustments and service improvements are made based on the data derived from cookies. Cookies are also sometimes used to save a user’s information so it doesn’t need to be re-entered each time the user visits.

The cookies we use on Bloggingheads.tv do not collect personally identifiable information. Currently we use cookies to limit the frequency with which a user is presented with pre-roll video ads. You may set your browser to refuse cookies from any website you visit. If you choose to do so, you should still have full use of Bloggingheads.tv, but you may see more frequent pre-roll video ads.

We also use the following Google services on Bloggingheads.tv, all of which employ cookies to collect nonpersonal information:

### Google Analytics

We use a third-party vendor, Google Analytics, to store and analyze cookies in order to make Bloggingheads.tv more interesting and useful to you. Information that we collect from these cookies is not used to create profiles of individual users and is used only in aggregate form. You may opt out of Google Analytics by using the [Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on](http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en).

### Google AdSense

AdSense is an advertising service provided by Google. We use this service to display ads on Bloggingheads.tv, which entails using the DoubleClick cookie to track user behavior concerning ads. The DoubleClick cookie enables Google and its partners to serve ads to you based on your visit to Bloggingheads.tv and/or other sites on the internet. This cookie does not track personal information about you such as your name or email address. You may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting Google’s [Ads Settings](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/).

### Google AdWords

We sometimes use the Google AdWords remarketing service to advertise on third-party websites (including Google) to previous visitors to our site. Such ads could appear on the Google search results page or on a site in the Google Display Network. We also use the “similar audiences” feature of AdWords, which targets our ads to people whose browsing patterns are similar to those of the Bloggingheads.tv audience.

## Your acceptance of these terms

By using Bloggingheads.tv, you signify your acceptance of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our website.

We may update this Privacy Policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the date at the bottom of this page. We encourage you to frequently check this page for any changes. Your continued use of Bloggingheads.tv following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

## Contact us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please send us a message on our contact form.

### The DMZ

## Bill Scher and Matt Lewis discuss Joe Biden and the emerging political advantage in refusing to apologize after gaffes or personal misconduct.

### The Glenn Show

## Michael Fortner describes his book _Black Silent Majority: The Rockefeller Drug Laws and the Politics of Punishment_ , about support for draconian drug laws in the black community in the 1970s.

### The Wright Show

## Chris Preble, author of the new book  _Peace, War, and Liberty: Understanding U.S. Foreign Policy_ , explains why his libertarian skepticism about military intervention isn’t the same as isolationism.

### Drezburt

## Heather Hurlburt and Dan Drezner discuss what the next Democratic president would do if Trump loses in 2020.

### The DMZ

## Matt Lewis explains why he would readily vote for libertarian GOP congressman Justin Amash, who is weighing a presidential run.

### Culturally Determined

## Chris Arnade, author of the new book _Dignity: Seeking Respect in Back Row America_ , discusses why many Americans don’t move away from where they grew up to seek better opportunities.
